hello and welcome everyone it is
November 2nd 2023 and blue and I are
here in ACM live stream
56.0 kicking off the 56 series on a set
of four
papers welcome to the active inference
Institute we are a participatory online
Institute that is communicating learning
and practicing applied active inference
you can find us at links here this is a
recorded and an archived live stream so
please provide feedback so we can
improve our work all backgrounds and
perspectives are welcome and we'll
follow video etiquette for live streams
head over to active infr.org if you want
to learn more about the Institute get
involved in any activities or learning
groups let's begin with a little bit of
an introduction and warmup say hello and
then maybe just one thing that we found
interesting in about these papers or
that made us want to jump in for the 56
series so I'm Daniel I'm a researcher in
California and I was very interested to
learn about what the relationship is
between different neural inspired
approaches to machine learning and
active inference
blue I mean same this kind of always
like the neurobiologically inspired um
machine learning is always kind of
something that peques my interest
and I'm still here still um excited
about it and uh in this like set of
papers I was actually like particularly
interested in like sparsity and how that
is maybe something that's particularly
biological or not or just kind of
learning in learning and Diving deeper
into sparsity as like a a topic of
consideration cool all right well in
this series and in this video we're
going to discuss four papers and we'll
get to why we have four soon four papers
are the neural coding framework for
learning generative models
2022 convolutional neural generative
coding scaling predictive coding to
Natural images
2022 spiking neural predictive coding
for continually learning from data
streams 2023 and Cog and gen building
the kernel for hyperdimensional
predictive processing cognitive
architecture
2022 and as there are four papers we're
going to use acronyms for each
paper and also go through them in this
order and again we'll return to why
there's four and why this order the four
acronyms are ncf 22 cgn c22 snpc 23 ppca
22 so the video is going to be an
introduction we're going to cover the
big questions and then basically jump
immediately into the four papers and
this is just an introduction feel free
to write comments or if you're around in
time to join for these upcoming
discussions that we're going to have
with author so blue what big questions
are you excited about
here um so I think I already talked
about sparcity but um I I would like to
know like what other types of tasks that
are perhaps maybe non-visual could
neurogenerative coding be suited to um
and then like the concept of in the last
paper we'll get to it of like a memory
Echo as a prediction I think like is
prediction just memory Echo and then
like that kind of leads
into um how like what is the difference
between I predict or I expect or I hope
right like I predict that the Eagles
might win the Super Bowl with like maybe
50 to 60% you know I I predict that's
like the the where I that's the
probability right 50 to 60% probability
that the Eagles win the Super Bowl but
like I totally hope that the Eagles win
a Super Bowl 100% so like where is the
the difference between hoping so and
like I can actually like I I thought
about it and it's like action the role
like you know you hope something happens
you hope you get into a good college you
predict that you'll go to college you
hope you get into a good college you you
know get good grades do all the things
and then you can act based on that hope
but like I actually can take no action
to effect whether or not the Eagles win
the Super Bowl so action's not
necessarily a key role there but like
how is Hope different from prediction
and expectation and how would you
approach modeling something like that
it's just something some something that
derailed me
anyway
interesting yep so my big questions
first just on the scope how how is it
different now that we're in our first
quadruple
do0 we've done one paper at once we've
done two at once side by side four is
double side by side and we love the four
about the topics though we are going to
get
very micro and zoomed
in and we're gonna have some of the
formalisms brought in but there's a lot
more in the paper so how do these
really
mechanistic Andor abstract micro level
discussions of like neuron
spiking help us get closer to real
cognitive architectures and modeling and
then I think to kind of
for um warn of the fourth paper here's
where we're going to see something like
the cognitive architecture that includes
not just perception and memory and all
these things but also the action
component so how does this connect to
active inference like is this driving
down the low road coming from the high
road is it another road so where is the
work that we're going to be looking at
in this sequence of research related to
basium mechanics free energy principle
some of these more first
principles intelligence conversations
that we have have so let's talk about
why there are four papers so I hope this
is okay that from aoria I share
something that he wrote he suggested the
four papers and said almost in that sort
of order from the more base neural
generative model coding predictive
coding framework ncf
22 that's going to be the first paper we
discuss to its convolutional
generalization cngc20
to down to its Spike level
generalization snpc
23 and back to its part in generalizing
active inference to a robotic setting
ppca 22 in a sort of progression SL
Series so hopefully this lays out our
approach to these four papers which we
were happy to accept this curriculum and
challenge the first paper that we're
going to to look at is going to set the
kind of Base Canvas OR overarching
umbrella
model the
NGC then there's going to be a
convolutional and a spike level
generalization or kind of additional
Motif and then we'll get to this
question of more integrated cognitive
modeling in the fourth bit any overall
thoughts just on the four papers split
before we go to the first one I mean I'm
curious to ask like what was the order
that these like started in and like how
like what like you know I mean sometimes
you just finish everything at once or
sometimes like you start something and
it takes forever so I'd like to know
like what were the order that the
projects were started in and as opposed
to like I mean we'd have the publication
dates and and whatever but I would like
to know like did they start and go in
this order just as like a narrative from
the
author that's a great question all right
first paper
neural coding framework for learning
generative models Aria and Keifer 2022
so just let me know when to switch
slides for this section blue thank you
awesome okay so we'll read the abstract
I'll go I'll just maybe I'll take a
couple senses and then pass it to you
Daniel if you don't mind um
neurogenerative models can be used to
learn complex probability distributions
from data to sample from them and to
produce probability density estimates we
propose a computational framework for
developing neurogenerative models
inspired by the theory of predictive
processing in the brain according to
predictive processing Theory the neurons
in the brain form a hierarchy in which
neurons in one level form expectations
about sensory inputs from another level
can read the rest these neurons update
their local models based on differences
between their expectations and the
observe signals in a similar way
artificial neurons in our generative
models predict what neighboring neurons
will do and adjust their parameters
based on how well the predictions match
reality in this work we show that the
neural generative models learned within
our framework perform well in practice
across several Benchmark data sets and
metrics and either remain competitive
with or significantly outperform other
generative models with similar
functionality such as variational Auto
encoder cool thanks so the road map this
is a nature paper and it's dense um so
there are like 18 different formalisms
in this paper and like many many
different models and sets of experiments
so the road map is here and we are not
going to go that deep into this because
we're doing four papers in you know
hopefully under 90 minutes um and so
we're going to go deep into the maths
here but hopefully we can get more heavy
into it in the dot one so pretty much
introduction results discussion and
methods but really what happens here is
um the results section kind of gives a
lot more introductory information about
like the back propagation and what
learning looks like in the brain and the
neural coding framework and how this
kind of you know forms a bridge here and
um then then training the model and how
the model updates everything and then
what can the model actually do so we're
going to kind of get into a little bit
about the model and what the model can
actually do and then Daniel I think will
delve deeper into the next couple of
papers into the model and then finally
tie it back into active inference um in
the paper so just that's an overall road
map and then the road map for this paper
too so go ahead and flip it to the next
one all right so in this paper the
author states that in neurobiological
systems neurons make use of the
information immediately available to
them in both time and space and do not
wait on distant regions in order to
adjust their synapses with Global
Information provided through
neurotransmitters such as
dopamine also later in the paper he says
while the question as to how credit
assignment is exact act ly implemented
in the brain is an open one it would
prove useful to machine learning
computational neuroscience and cognitive
science to have a framework that
demonstrates how a neural system can
learn something as complex as a
generative model without back
propagation using mechanisms and rules
that our brain inspired so that's kind
of what they set out to do in this paper
so let's go ahead and flip
it so here this is figure one and this
is like Figure 1 a uh looking at a back
propagation model and so this is I from
the legend in the figure he says credit
assignment in back propagation or in
backr I I won't keep uh elongating that
credit assignment in backprop requires a
strict Global feedback pathway which
requires the completion of the forward
pass that carries information Upstream
right to left this feedback pathway
carries the error message ezo at the
output layer back along left to right
the same synapses used in the forward
pass to update Downstream n neurons Z1
and Z2 back prop differs from brain like
learning because so this is it within
the paper not the Legend um the synapses
that make up the forward information
pathway need to be directly used in
Reverse to communicate teaching signals
which is the this is known as the weight
transport problem and so you can see
that here so here it's going from left
to right like the output layer is here
at e0 or the error message is here at e0
and then the back propag happens is here
at this red arrow thank you Daniel as
I'm pointing to the screen you're
following my finger along um okay
neurons need to know about and
communicate their own activation
functions first derivative um and that
is shown here in the little um Deltas so
neurons must wait for the neurons ahead
of them to percolate their own error
signals backwards before they know when
or how to adjust their own synapses and
this is known as the update locking
problem and then also there is a
distinct form of information propagation
for error feedback one that starts from
the system's output and works its way
back to the input layer so that's shown
here in figure one which does not
influence neural activity so in other
words the global feedback pathway
problem backrop creates signals that
only affect weights but do not at least
directly affect or improve the network
the Network's representation of the
environment so it seems like a lot of
extra steps um and then the error
signals have a one toone correspondence
with neurons so we can flip to the next
slide so in this paper the first four of
those points are addressed by
neurogenerative coding so everything
except the final point the Ono one
correspondence between the error signal
and the neuron so this is the
neurogenerative coding model so it says
the proposed NGC model sidesteps this
neurobiologically implausible
requirement by learning with short local
aor transmission Pathways pathways that
are made possible through recurrent
error synapses and stateful neural
activities credit assignment under
neural generative coding operates with
local mismatch signals E1 and E2 that
readily communicate this information to
their respective layers Z1 and Z2 so
here the black arrows are forward
propagation while the red arrows are
backwards transmission solid lines
indicate that a signal is transformed
along a synapse while Dash lines
indicate direct copying of information
so it's like the identity function no
transformation of the signal um and then
the the Delta show the communication of
the neuron's first derivative the
triangle represents the computed change
to the synapse of the forward pass that
will use the nearby error signal and
then the dot is the multiplication of
incoming signals which you see those all
like we don't see the dot here but it's
in the um back propop model so in the
previous one okay so that's the model
that's all we're going to talk about for
this so far so far so we're going to see
now like what are the different models
that they compared against so I'm just
going to list them right here um so they
used back propop models the regular
regularized Auto encoder and these are
the um abbreviations that are used here
the gaussian variational auto encoder
the constant various constant variance
Gan variational Auto encoder um the
adversarial autoencoder and then the
Deep sparse rectifier Network and that's
purely discriminate ly trained so I just
want to point that out and it'll be
important as we get later just the last
one um and then the neurogenerative
coding models so this is actually um the
first one is from the like super seminal
row and Ballard 1999 paper um and then
also a super seminal paper by frisen in
2008 and then the later two models which
we'll talk about more in the one are
models that are developed by the authors
of this paper so these GN CN models are
both um developed by the author and then
the gaussian mixture model is like just
another classic Benchmark model that's
not back propagation or um the
generative coding it's it's just yeah a
mixture of a g gaussian distribution so
okay next so what can these models do so
generative neural coding can learn
viable autoassociative generative models
and let's check out some of the results
that they got all right so here we are
table one so I gave you all the models
so that you can kind of see what's over
here so the only ones that are um
neurogenerative coding are the gncn ones
so the last four and then the first two
the first one's from the raal paper that
says raal and then the second one with
the sigma is the friston so we see here
the the regularized autoencoder
autoassociative network least equipped
to serve as a data synthesizer um has a
lower error lower reconstruction error
in terms of binary cross entropy be
compared to the other back propagation
generative models so the other GV AE
ones um and then while the variational
autoencoder models yield worse
reconstruction than the regularized
autoencoder they obtain much better log
likelihoods um especially compared to
the gaussian mixed model Baseline
indicating that they are strong data
Samplers um and then the neurogenerative
coding models the ones developed by the
authors here obtain comp itive log
likelihood with the variational
autoencoder
models um and with the GN CN pdh yields
the best log likelihood of all of them
for all four data sets and so the data
sets that they're talking about here
we're going to see some pictures of them
in a little bit but they're um like the
number data sets the m n IST so not all
of them are numbers so mnist is like the
classic number data set um and then the
fmn is like pieces of clothes and then
the Caltech one is like I don't know
some strange shapes so let's flip to the
next one and maybe it'll show us I think
it does actually oh no let's flip let's
flip to back to figure four so we can
look at the data sets or to figure the
next one yeah and then we'll flip back
yeah let's let's see the data sets there
you go perfect so sorry I should have
reordered these but you can see I'm
trying to describe these samples so this
one is like some like handwriting I'm
not sure is that a language Daniel the
kmn do you
know no you don't it's not any language
I was like is it like I don't know is it
Chinese Arabic I could I can't read it
so I don't know um but you can see here
the MN is numbers the fmn is is closed
the C and like the rest are just like
symbolic representations so just so you
guys know this is what they're looking
at this is what they're trying to
generate so then let's go back to figure
four oh there we go okay so figure four
this is the error the BCE loss
measurements so lower is better
for pattern reconstruction on data
subsets so this is measured in terms of
the percentage of the original database
sampled so here you can see the the BCE
loss which is like we want less less is
better for all of the different
um models here shown so the Rae is blue
the variational um is light green the
Gan um AE that's like another Auto
encoder that is dark green and then this
three the pink purple and orange are
neurogenerative coating models from
friston and then the two um shown here
so like they're not always they don't
always show every model in every figure
but you can see here that the error for
the three like the pink pink orange pink
pink orange is pretty low all the way
across the board here so I think that
that's the important um result and then
let's we can flip on so neural
generative coding also yields strong
Downstream pattern classifiers so let's
see how the authors found
that um in table two in terms of test
error uh we can see them all here so
here's the different models the dsrn is
the discriminatively trained model and
then that's the auto encoder the back
these are all the back propagation ones
the first four and then the last four
are the neurogenerative coding models um
with the final two being the ones used
here developed here by the authors so we
can see the data sets so the top two of
each the top two um pictures in each row
are the data sets like from the original
data and then the bottom two are
generated by um the model so we can see
that that this is how they are like how
they're generating the sample so um here
the the bottom two um even the the very
bottom one oh wait yeah the bottom three
are competitive with the purely
discriminatively trained model the top
one which has the best um output and
they outperform all of the generative
models even the dsrn in one case so the
bottom the bottom model bottom two
models do really well um in generating
data so good uh and then figure six I
think shows kind of the same thing so in
figure 6A this is a teasy plot of the
data and the data clustering so we
provide qualitative evidence that the
latent represent present ations of
neurogenerative coding this is from the
ncn pdh they appear to yield a stronger
natural separation of the test data into
class respective clusters compared with
the back propagation based model which
was this was the best performing back
propop model with respect to log
likelihood and reconstruction error so
we can see that there's like a more
distinct clustering here um and I think
that that's that's what uh the authors
are saying is the qualitative evidence
again we emphasize that the
neurogenerative coding model acquired
representations without labeled
information so the class-based
relationships have emerged as a result
of very sparse neural activities this is
why like I'm so interested in the
sparsity here um this offers some
promising evidence that the
neurogenerative coding models
representations offer benefits beyond
the original density estimation task
allowing reuse of the same system for
Downstream tasks like
categorization so pretty
neat um and then neurogenerative coding
can conduct pattern completion we'll
click on the next one um so this they
didn't show uh the data here they showed
like a little bit in the methods um but
they said that another interesting
ability attributed to autoassociative
memory models associative memory models
is their ability to complete partially
corrupted or incomplete patterns um and
they hypothesized that a neural
generative coding model's ability to
conduct pattern completion better than
the autoencoder models is due to its
iterative inference processes so I'd
like to see future work that kind of
probes at this a little
bit thank you blue that's super helpful
very nice any other comments on the
paper
no yeah they replaced this time lock
weight transport bound Global feedback
constraint setting with a biologically
inspired locally
computable etc etc
architecture that is kind of the base
case that we're now going to dive into
two specifications or elaborations of
convolutional first then Spike level and
then in the fourth paper it's going to
come back to mainly blue with the
overview of the cognitive
architecture okay can you read the
abstract for this one sure uh in this
work we develop convolutional
neurogenerative coding con NGC a
generalization of predictive coding to
the case of convolution deconvolution
based computation specifically we
correctly Implement a flexible
neurobiologically motivated algorithm
that progressively refines lat and state
feature maps in order to dynamically
form a more accurate internal
representation SL reconstruction model
of natural images the performance of the
resulting sensory processing system is
evaluated on complex data sets such as
the color minced sear 10 and Street
house view numbers we study the
effectiveness of our brain inspired
model on the tasks of reconstruction and
image den noising and find that it is
competitive with convolutional auto
encoding systems train by back back
propagation of errors and outperforms
them with respect to outof distribution
reconstruction including the full
90k syic 10 test
set thank you so this paper is somewhat
similar and related to the previous
paper except as promised it's going to
generalize it into the convolutional
setting so there's also a lot of
nice Exposition in this paper so it will
be good to get some background too
introduction then the convolutional
neural generative coding model details
on the theory and the practice of the
experiments about what was tested and
done and they summarize contributions as
follows one we propose a new neural
perception model Comm
NGC which acquires robust
representations of natural images in an
unsupervised fashion two
to the best of our knowledge this is the
first work in the literature where
visual inputs are processed using deep
deconvolutional layers directly and
naturally within a framework of
predictive coding significantly
enhancing its representation power for
vision-based tasks and three we
demonstrate on several natural image
data sets that the proposed con NGC is
competitive with existing back prop
based models of similar architectural
designs on the tasks of image
reconstruction and image den noising and
outperforms them with respect to outo
distribution
prediction so some of the first
sentences of this paper that set the
stage really well the first sentence
begins with back propagation and
highlighting that while it's done well
writing on the tide of increasing power
of hardware and software there are still
some
limitations associated with backprop
based AI the field still has a long way
to go towards developing artificial
general intelligence I think it'll be an
interesting question is that what this
field or who in this field means what by
that in order to increase task level
performance the size of deep networks
has increased greatly over the years up
to hundreds of billions of synaptic
parameters as seen in modern-day
Transformer
networks this scaling is all you need
Paradigm increases the number of
parameters and the deployment of
multiple MO
like Transformer architectures attention
motifs so on as well as changing and
curing data sets and we are now getting
up to models in the 2020s that have
billions of
parameters however this trend has
started to raise concerns related to
energy
consumption and
more energy consumption limited
flexibility and generalization limited
biological
plausibility and this results in some
computational constraints and
limitations especially around
parallelization Federation learning all
these kinds of settings that we want to
have effective algorithms for so people
are looking into different methods
biologically based and otherwise that
speak to different aspects of
this they right some of the most
promising Pathways in addressing all
those problems listed previously come
from the emerging domain of research
known as brain inspired computation
which seeks to develop neural
architectures and their respective
credit assignment algorithms that
leverage only local information
motivated strongly by how learning is
conducted in the brain the promise of
brain inspired Computing brings with it
synaptic adjustment mechanisms that are
neurobiologically grounded as well as
neural computation and inference that is
flexible capable providing a wide
variety of operations at biologically
more faithful levels facilitating
massive algorithmic parallelization at
scale and adaption on analog and
neuromorphic Hardware so it's an
interesting discussion topics what
aspects or Properties or processes or
features or perspectives are we trying
to copy about the brain and while we
were preparing for this in some open
sessions someone told me about this spy
kid's third brain and this kind of
Designing a brain and what does it mean
to really design cognitive
architectures what does it mean to
consider diverse
intelligences how is this related to the
kinds of large scale scientific research
projects that are going on in the human
brain any thoughts on that
blue
okay at the end of the introduction they
again summarize their contributions that
we looked at previously and before we
jump in this is from the appendix of the
paper here here's some key symbol
operator abbreviation definitions in
table three little bit of exposure to
the symbols we're going to
see section two convolutional neural
generative coding we start by describing
our model instantiation of a
convolutional neural generative coding
con MVC which is tasked with learning
from streams of natural images in an
unsupervised fashion typically in a
visual recognition task input patterns
belonging to different object classes or
arranged into batches are presented to a
processing system at different time
points for
training here they formalize the problem
and give a bit more information on the
notation conf NGC is a generalization of
the NGC computational framework from 41
that was the ncf 22 paper that we just
heard about generalizing it to the case
of natural image data so in those other
data sets like mnist and others every
pixel is just passed in of a relatively
small image so that the whole image can
be taken in as a matrix like a binary
Matrix with black and white squares or a
grayscale matrix however real visual
data coming in for example off of a
camera sensor is apt to have much higher
resolution and so a biologically
inspired design pattern that we find in
the retina and other kinds of biological
visual s aners is this idea of
convolution where a convolving function
is used to blur and essentially get a
Core graining across a highresolution
visual input the underlying process of
con NGC can be divided into three
components local prediction and error
unit map calculation Laten state map
correction and local synaptic adjustment
so this is drawing on the architecture
and the motifs that were introduced
previously
bringing in convolution so that natural
images can be
addressed here's the con NGC model it
consists of a set of L predictive
layers typically arranged hierarchically
though this is not a strict
architectural requirement EG figure one
depicts a non-h hierarchical NGC circuit
so that was figure
one here's figure
two which is I guess a more
hierarchically structured con NGC with
three
layers section three goes into more
detail on this model in this section we
provide concrete implementation details
of the neural coding process described
earlier depicting how layer-wise State
prediction state correction and synoptic
parameter updating occurs specifically
in the context of visual object
reconstruction the first two steps of
the algorithm iteratively predicting
correct the representations of the con
NGC model for observed input values
natural images of the current data
set after T iterations the final step
entails adjusting model synaptic
efficacies using simple heavan like
updates so these are the three main
steps there's a two-stroke Engine with
prediction and
correction kind of like an expectation
maximization and then after a certain
number of iterations T there's the
adjustment of Sy aptic efficacies so
here is from the appendix this is the
pseudo code of the
algorithm section 3.1 inference
predicting and correcting neural States
going through those steps layer-wise
state map prediction and state map
correction then 3.2 training updating
the models
parameters having described the model
essentially they go to section four the
experiment
We compare con NGC to powerful back prop
based models such as the convolutional
autoencoder denoising convolutional
autoencoder as well as the fully
connected form of neural generative
coding which under certain conditions
recovers the unsupervised form of the
model in 55 which is salvatory at all
hierarchical predictive coding
Network details are provided about the
data sets used and tables 1 and two
provide some performance measures
evaluated in terms of mean squared error
structural similarity index measures and
Peak signal to noise
ratios one can look to the tables to see
where the different models do well or
not um here are figures four and three
figure three shows an image randomly
sampled from a data set left the same
image corrupted with noise so here's the
original image a five and some kind of
object and then a digitally corrupted
version with a normally distributed
noise term added and then after
processing this is the denoised
image that's figure three figure four
feature maps for the bottom three layers
of a trained con NGC model so this just
shows a little bit of kind of the inner
work workings of the
model and surprisingly with respect to
the outof distribution experiments o con
NGC outperforms all the Baseline
models this desirable Improvement is
indicated by the higher trial averaged
out of distribution Peak signal to noise
ratio as well as the structural
similarity
scores what is most impressive is that
the con NGC model was trained on natural
images in the housing numbers data set
that did not contain any of the objects
found within either CFR 10 and synic 10
and was still able to reconstruct with
top performance this result offers a
promising future Direction worth
exploring for con NGC and NGC predictive
coding systems in general their ability
to generalize to unseen patterns that
violate the assumption that they were
generated by a distribution similar to
that of a training data so this is I
think is going to be interesting
discussion point it's kind of like if
you classified a vision ual detector
based upon only a data set with a
certain kind of edge or Surface then
it's possible that the model wouldn't
learn more General features of edges and
surfaces it might be able to use a back
propagation type updating and credit
assignment Paradigm so that something
really really high level and Abstract
like whether it's a cat or a dog could
be tagged with something very micro
which is overfit to to cats versus dogs
or even more locally like that cat
versus that dog data set and so
potentially constraining to these local
connections only making a kind of
enforced sparity means that the messages
that get past are not just more
biologically plausible and fewer of them
but potentially they extract features
more like the visual system does in
terms of extracting generalized edges
and
features through lower
level features that kind of percolate up
into higher level features in a really
methodical way which is why we can like
recognize a shape that we've never seen
before so in conclusion here's the whole
conclusion our results mark an important
step towards crafting more robust
General brain inspired neural
architectures and learning processes
capable of handling complex machine
learning tasks so some questions for
discussion are written here and there
are three very informative appendices in
this paper so for more detail if you
think this is cool definitely read the
paper check out the
appendices on to the third
paper this is snpc 23 you want to add
anything on that
blue spiking neural predictive coding
for continually learning from data
streams do you want to read the
abstract sure uh for energy efficient
computation in specialized neuromorphic
Hardware we present spiking neural
coding an instantiation of a family of
artificial neural models grounded in the
theory of predictive coding this model
the first of its kind works by operating
in a never-ending process of guess and
check where neurons predict the activity
values of one another and then adjust
their own activities to make better
future predictions the iterative
interactive nature of our system fits
well into the continuous time
formulation of sens sensory stream
prediction and as we show the model
structure yields a local synaptic update
rule which can be used to complement or
as an alternative to online Spike timing
dependent plasticity in this article we
experiment with an instantiation of our
model consisting of leaky integrate and
fire units integrate and fire units
however the framework within which our
system is situated can naturally
incorporate more complex neurons such as
the hodkin Huxley model our experimental
results in pattern recognition
demonstrate the potential of the model
when binary Spike trains are the primary
Paradigm for interneuron communication
notably spiking neural coding is
competitive in terms of classification
performance and experiences less
forgetting when learning from a task
sequence offering a more computationally
economical biologically motivated
alternative to popular artificial neural
networks awesome thank
you okay here's the road map and a key
piece of this paper so they start with
the introduction then go to the
methodology Define the problem really
well and introduce the spiking neural
coding framework in order to implement
this kind of continual error correction
from the spike trains section three
covers the experimental results
simulations and limitations then there's
conclusion and an appendix they write in
this paper we propose spiking neural
coding as well as a concrete model
instantiation that is composed of leaky
integrate and fire neurons and its
learning process for adjusting synaptic
weight strengths incrementally although
we only examined one kind of spiking
neuron our general framework can
accommodate simulated neural models of
varying complexity so it's going to be a
simple version of spiking with a binary
Spike train and a leaky integrate and
fire neuron however there's even sub
generalizations within this spiking
Paradigm so just as a kind of reminder
we introduced the Gen General local
compute only predictive coding
architecture in the first paper second
paper looked into the convolutional
generalization both the first and the
second paper though were trained in
essentially batch mode training data
sets were loaded in and they were
trained in a sort of batch based
approach here through this spiking
mechanism think about a trace through
time and spikes happening along that
timeline the data are coming in not in a
batch that the computer gets to process
at the kind of pace or way it wants but
rather the data are coming in real time
so this generalization is much more fit
to both the real time like Internet of
Things semantic spatial web setting but
also the biological perception
setting here there's a similar
introduction instead of just harping on
backprop though artificial neural
networks Ann's are the models which are
described in terms of being very large
and Powerful but with challenges and
surprise surprise people are using brain
inspired Computing to formalize and
Implement various times kinds of neural
computation and learning mechanisms
currently known in cognitive
neuroscience and we only bring a few of
these onto the slides but I have been
taking many sections of text and passing
it through different image generators so
it's always fun to like see the visual
semantics of what sometimes these
otherwise really wordy sections are
about so section two 2.1 problem
definition continually predicting
sensory stream inputs so this is the key
difference spiking is a motif or an
architecture that is going to enable us
to move from the batch based setting to
the real time or the online setting the
neural agents that we are ultimately
concerned with process C sensory
stimuli which are sampled from an
environment or a stochastic process over
time so here we see a really nice
connection to epistemic foraging
information foraging in active inference
and here are some specifications of what
is meant by that and also more about the
data stream formulation it still treat
each data point as a discrete element
the spiking neural networks are intended
to process input stimuli that arrive
with A continuous flow of time in order
to truly adapt the above stream to the
spiking neural net we further generalize
the setting so that each Tuple is
presented to the learner for a fixed
period of simulated time and the length
of the stimulus and Inter stimulus times
will vary depending on the data problem
and application so it's not the case
that it's just an infinitely short
flash it's the case that it's there for
a defined amount of time kind of like a
video frame so if a video is 25 or 30
frames per second then that is in this
sort of 30 to 50 millisecs range of
presentation of a given
stimuli so that allows the connection
between the frequency of the
regularities in the pattern in the
environment to be connected to the rate
of updating and of like the real
biophysics of neuronal membranes or of
some neuromorphic computer 2.2 gives a
mechanis IC description of the spiking
neural coding
Network so this is the spiking base
generalization more formalisms and
information here's what it looks like in
figure one a two- layer spiking neural
coding Network architecture we see a lot
of motifs from the previous papers this
kind of local Loop and the ease and
disease green diamonds indicate the
error units
e which in this simplified model
depiction compute the amount of mismatch
between the current predictions which
are the
Z's of subm and the target signal traces
Z's of T variables s represent the
binary Spike outputs of a particular
Vector grouping of neural units at time
T so more formalisms are provided and
just like the last paper there is an
algorithm in the
appendix here's what the SPN CN
algorithm looks
like figure two I'm just overlaying
figure one just on top it's not meant to
Overlay it directly but just to remember
that this is the kind of architecture
that Spike trains are being pass through
or are occurring within so figure two is
showing these kind of biologically
reasonable despite the simple integrate
and fire
model traces kind of like a single
neuron recording from inside of this
little in silico brain section three in
silico uh results with the model
simulation first they looked at the
mnist the digit classification data set
they presented two sets of experiments
that tested the SPN cn's ability to
generate and classify patterns as well
as its ability to retain knowledge over
task sequence and the appendix has more
experiments so table one two and three
have different evaluations and scores
and then also just like the tne that
blue mentioned in the first paper here's
a tne now of the SPN
CN with access to mnist training up
front in the middle the continual SPN CN
and a continual SPN CN with a buff
versus the lat so we'll go into more
detail with these subvariants but here
we can see that this realtime learning
is actually
recapitulating similar structure
and near enough similar learning um
performance as batch Learners which is a
big theme of the
paper so here is a figure five showing
task accuracy normalized to 01 over
proportion of a current task data and so
on the x-axis is the portion of the task
completed on the Y AIS is the accuracy
range so here it's shown for the three
SPN CN
variance but that was done for not just
one data set but that was actually done
for a whole set of data sets in figure 5
and so the big takeaway from this whole
figure is that SPN CN obtains
competitive cross task performance even
though it is trained online it only
processes data patterns once whereas to
obtain top performance rate coded
baselines were trained on each task for
multiple
Epoch pretty cool and then figure four
again is a tne layout of these different
model variants
3.2 describes some limitations and then
the conclusion in this paper we propose
spiking neural coding as well as a
concrete model instantiation composed of
leaky integrating and fire neurons and
its learning process for adjusting
synaptic weight strengths incrementally
pattern classification and continual
learning experiments demonstrate the
generalization ability of our model in
the realm of online continuous time
based learning and the model is
competitive with many spiking neural
networks learned with Spike time
dependent plasticity
stdp or other mechanism further our
model exhibits better computational
economy and is more biologically
plausible than modern-day non-spiking
artificial neural networks and then
it'll be cool to discuss future work so
to kind of close this paper and head
into our fourth one we started with a
big picture with predictive coding
things that we've talked about in many
live streams we just heard in the last
two papers ERS the
convolutional extension which enables
higher resolution naturalistic images
and then this spiking variant which
brings it into the setting of Real Time
online learning through spiking which
also has lower energy requirements than
non-spiking neural networks and now back
to Blue for the fourth paper Cog and Jen
building the kernel for a
hyperdimensional pred to processing
cognitive
architecture cool thanks Daniel that was
neat um do you want to read this
abstract
sure we present a new cognitive
architecture that combines two
neurobiologically plausible
computational elements one a variant of
predictive processing known as neural
generative coding NGC and two
hyperdimensional SL Vector symbolic
models of human memory we draw
inspiration from well-known cognitive
architectures such as act R sore leabra
and spound
Neno our cognitive architecture the
cognitive neural generative system Cogen
gen is in Broad agreement with these
architectures but provides a level of
detail between act R's high level
symbolic description of human cognition
and span's lowlevel neurobiological
description Cogen gen creates the
groundwork for developing agents that
learn continually from diverse tasks
and model human performance at larger
scales than what is possible with
existent cognitive
architectures we aim to develop a
cognitive architecture that has the
power of modern machine learning
techniques while retaining long-term
memory single trial planning transfer
learning planning and other capacities
associated with high level cognition we
test Cog anden on a set of maze learning
tasks including mazes that test
short-term memory and planning and find
that the Synergy between its predictive
processing and Vector symbolic
components of allow it to master the
maze tasks future work includes testing
Cog and gen on more tasks and exploring
methods for efficiently scaling
hyperdimensional memory models to
lifetime
learning cool thanks so much um so
unlike the first paper where we talked
very little about the model and a lot
about the tests and results we're going
to talk um a lot about the model and
very little about the tests and results
in in this paper so um kind of dive a
little bit deeper in here
uh okay do you want to flip through to
the next one all right so the authors
claim they they propose a cognitive
architecture that is built on Two
neurobiologically And cognitively
plausible models namely a variant of
predictive processing known as neural
generative coding um from this 2020
paper which we did not go into here
today uh and Vector symbolic also known
as hyperdimensional models of memory um
and we're going to talk a lot about this
Hinman 198 six um model it's called
minurva 2 and then a few other
references here okay so this is the
common model of cognition and this is
like a conglomeration of all these
different references that are here in
The Legend um and it just shows like
there's some commonalities that go like
across different um cognition system
models okay so you have declarative
long-term memory um also that's
associated with the hippocampus and the
temporal lobe and here um that's
achieved with manura 2 there is um
working memory which is the front of
parietal network uh they did this with
manura 2 or the self recurrent slot
buffer um which we'll talk about later
later later um and then there's
procedural memory uh that's associated
with the basil ganglia done with
neurogenerative coding here perception
and action so finally we get to
perception and action after uh you know
what are we an hour deep so far or an
hour in so finally we're here at
perception in action we've arrived so
perception is the sensory cores um and
action is the motor cortex and both of
these are achieved with the neural
generative coding
model next
slide cool okay so we talk about a lot
of neural building blocks um I mean I
think that we just went through kind of
all of the cognitive architecture
building blocks um and here I just to
kind of get into the model a little bit
so this first equation one is at the top
right okay so given an input output pair
of sensory vectors XI and XO where X is
the in x i is the input and XO is the
output the circuit clamps the last layer
ZL so you see that up here in equation
one to the input and clamps the first
first layer z0 to the
output once clamped the neurogenerative
coding circuit will undergo a settling
cycle where it processes the input and
output vectors for K steps in time so it
processes sensory signals over a
stimulus window of K discrete time steps
so that's just kind of like a broad
overview of how the system is working um
e is a matrix with error synapses that
passes M mismatch signals across the
layers from L minus one to L um and then
let's look so beta is the neural State
update coefficient that's set according
to one over to where to is the
integration time constant in the order
of milliseconds so here you can see that
this update equation indicates that a
vector of neural activity changes at
each step within a settling cycle
according to from left to right in
equation one a leak term modulated by
gamma the bottom pressure from match
signals in lower level regions and a top
down pressure from the neural region
above so that's kind of how this
algorithm is working in a in a short
summary kind of way okay do you want to
flip to the next
one okay so neural building blocks
adding to memory so this is this
reference that I told you we were going
to talk a lot about from 1984 I think
it's some it said 1986 somewhere maybe
there's like an updated model um but
manura 2 stores memory traces
observations or sequences of
observations of the state of the world
each memory Trace is represented as an
array of real numbers a vector manura 2
stores all memory traces separately as
rows in a continuously growing table we
use manura 2's forgetting mechanism oh
that's the 1986 reference to randomly
delete values from memory each time
memory is updated at sufficiently high
probability to impose a computationally
tractable limit on the size of the
memory so if there was no forgetting
there would be like this would be an
impossible problem just an impossible
method by which to store the memory okay
next so this is how you get things out
of memory so in manura 2 memory
retrieval is not a lookup process it's a
reconstruction Pro process so when a
retrieval Quee or a probe is presented
like the smell of chocolate chip cookies
um each Vector in the memory t T is
activated in proportion to its
similarity to the Q so similarity is
computed as a normalized dotproduct of
the q's Vector with the stored Vector so
every stored Vector is activated by its
similarity to the probe raised to a
power and by raising the similarity to
some power the contribution of the most
similar vectors is
emphasized um and then this is the what
I was talking about at the very
beginning about an echo um so it says
here an echo is retrieved from memory as
a way ated sum so that's this equation
in the top right so where me is the echo
or the output for memory Mi is the I
trace in memory MP is the probe or input
to memory and M is the number of traces
in the memory
table um and so we're going to look in
the next slide about um so is is like
prediction just an echo from memory so
we're going to look at that maybe here
oh yeah it's here
so it says in kogan genen we combine
insights from several versions of manura
2 we make an architecture wide
commitment to predict then correct
learning predict then correct can be
implemented in manura 2 as discrepancy
in coding given a sequence of the
observations manura 2 can predict the
next observation based on past
experience after the prediction a new
observation is made we update memory
with the difference between observation
MX and prediction me so wasn't that just
an echo it's prediction an echo for
memory like I think that that's what's
what they're saying here um
so MX minus me so observation minus
prediction such that if the prediction
is correct no change is made to memory
whereas if the prediction is wrong that
prediction is inhibited in similar
future
contexts this is awesome I I I I love
that you're pulling on this kind of Echo
and prediction of memory because it's
also related to how we learn like we
predict then correct and that's kind of
like the prepare
measure learn Quantum information
Quantum fvp
connection but then H how how rich could
a learning experience be if we predicted
what do you think the next slide's going
to be like and then I learn about you I
learn about the paper and then no skin
in the game it comes up I I was off
because I didn't know you learn that's
the update and then you learn on the
learning so there's no end to how many
layers you could learn with just like
one data
point right like what's my prediction of
the next slide I theoretically have that
in my memory as an echo somewhere but
it's not coming to mind so I'll find out
when we get
there all right here we are so shortterm
versus long-term memory um so for Cog
and Jen we adopt Collins at out 2020
approach and model both working and
declarative memory using manura 2 our
working manura 2 is cleared after a task
is completed for example a maze is
solved whereas the contents of the
declarative manura 2 which serves as the
episodic memory in this paper's
instantiation of of kogen persist across
tasks so there's some memory clear when
the task is over yeah short-term memory
that gets cleared after like each each
example like each question on a test
each maze but then the
declarative way of knowing is being kept
episodically so like a memory of solving
that maze is stored declaratively but
each maze is each only being addressed
with the working memory so it's
cool um so there's not a lot here in the
perception um place so um they say that
the environment that they investigate
which is Jim minigrid which is an open
AI environment so if you guys are
interested you can go check out open AI
JY minigrid um but it provides a fixed
problem specific encoder Fe and decoder
FG so they use a fixed encoding and
decoding scheme to simplify the
simulation and future work is going to
investigate learning the perception
modules as neurogenerative coding
circuits instead so they didn't do that
for this paper next paper that's da da
coming
okay so neurogenerative procedural
memory action selection is driven by
changes in the neural activity of Basil
ganglia which estimate the value of the
expected reward um and these authors
were motivated by the finding of
expected value estimation in the brain
so they made the Cog and jens's
procedural module Implement a neural
Circ neural circuit that produces
intrinsic reward signals at a high level
this neurom Machinery facilitates some
of the functionality offered by the
basil ganglia and procedural memory
simulating and an internal reward
creation process so they say we
Implement a neurogenerative coding
Dynamics model from which a reward
signal is calculated as a function of
its own error neurons we couple the
Dynamics model with a short-term memory
module based on manura 2 which adjusts
the reward value produced by the dynamic
Circuit by determining if an observed
state is famili or
not yeah and then well just you're
laging gonna see that in a figure in the
next figure okay I'm just I'm GNA let
your internet just
return okay BL I shut off my video okay
okay yeah the only comment on this is um
this idea of the intrinsic reward signal
happening from a procedural module yeah
I'm good can you hear me yeah so it's
like epistemic foraging you have a
procedure for
foraging and then there's an intrinsic
reward even arising just by carrying out
the procedure which might be the predict
and learn and reflect.
0.1.2 with an intrinsic smooth reward
signal rather than kind of a needle in
the hay stack more like
being just in a continuous
flow is your internet
back I think so can you hear me okay yes
figure three then continue okay now you
can hear me yep go good okay perfect I
just I turned off my video so if I get
the flash again I'll turn it off because
sometimes it's easier okay figure
three perfect so um and just what you
were saying about the intrinsic reward
before I delve into figure three um they
did talk a little bit in this paper and
I don't know if I pushed it into here
but maybe we'll get into it in the dot
too um but they did talk about uh trying
to push exploration via an intrinsic
reward signal so we can kind of get into
that exploration exploitation um
discussion in the dot two a little bit
more okay so figure three the kogen
Dynamics model um it says that arrows
transform data across Sim across
synapses
um and then the gray circles represent
stateful neurons and the green diamonds
represent error neurons so this is
um the
multi-layer uh model that we're looking
at here with an
external input and Z of
T and we can see the layers across time
so I think it's maybe it says more in
the next slide let's see so building
upon the notion planning its inference
uh we generalize neurogenerative coding
to the case of action-driven tasks which
we call Active neurogenerative coding
notably within the neurogenerative
coding Action Motor model is a
modifiable working memory that allows
the model to store a finite quantity of
projected Laten State vectors into a set
of self-recurrent memory Vector slots
this particular working memory module
which we call the self-recurrent slot
buffer serves as the glue that joins the
models of COG and genen together so we
talked we heard about the slot buffer a
long time ago and here we back to the
slot buffer um and then in the next
figure we're going to look at the action
driven task in the next
figure perfect so this is the motor
model where the internal control portion
produces signals those are the C NT that
manipulate working memory and the
external control pushes transmit
transmits signals so this is the cext
down at the bottom that affect the
environment and so both the internal and
external control share the same working
memory which is
interesting so explicit declarative
memory episodic memory um so kogen
implements a replay mechanism in the
form of an episodic memory constructed
with manura information is transferred
to memory through an intermediate
working buffer where pieces of the
transition are progressively stored as
they are encountered through the agent
environment interaction process we do
not update the motor action and Dynamics
models online but instead update their
parameters only when episodic me memory
is sampled thus the kogan genen
computational process has two phases at
each time step of the simulation the
processing step and the learning step
and so we'll see figure two I think I
have it
next yeah perfect I I reordered them
because um they were mentioned in in
different orders in the
um in the paper so Daniel showed this to
us
earlier um do you want to maybe talk a
little bit about this figure while I go
grab my computer plug yeah you mind cool
well few ways to look at it one of them
is we're dealing with this fundamental
interface question blanket question
boundary
question which is how we begin in active
inference and free energy principle
about the agents in their boundedness
interfacing with the
environment and then while we might see
this in a partially observable marov
decision process generative model here
we basically see the formalism from the
last several papers this paper
specifically being represented in the
way that we've seen Agent environment
interface before observation coming in
at time step T lat and space here it's
actually a more sophisticated latent
space it's not just like one gaussian
parameter that's getting updated there's
this entire dialectic with the
procedural and the working memory and
the episodic all these cognitive
features and then there there is motor
or action control action is emitted
within the time step and then there's
the observation at the next time step so
this is
a cognitive
architecture that brings together a lot
of the features that we've been talking
about plus these higher order structured
purely cognitive
aspects thanks you so
much um my computer thanks you as well
so this um
I so I'm curious here in this model how
things get from the working memory into
the episodic memory so I would like to
see like maybe more details about that
as we go into the dot two
um yeah okay so in the mini grid world
problem um they are investigating two
tasks uh to evaluate the agents that
they used so one is the door ke key task
the DK task and the other is the memory
task so everybody's in a grid it's a
partially observable view of the
agents's environment um and there's a
three-channel
object um yeah so the agents environment
is a three Channel object a tensor
created by mapping each visible grid
cell to three integer values so
everything each tile contains either
nothing one object and a discrete object
type so ultimately
tile is encoded to an object index so
it's unseen empty wall and then a color
index red green whatever and then a
state index which is open closed or
locked so those are the three um three
yeah things three things three things in
the environment okay next
so the agent is restricted to picking up
one single object a key and may open a
lock door if it carries a key that
matches the door color so that's the
door key problem the discrete action
space for the agent is six actions turn
left right forward pick up an object or
drop the object that it's currently
carrying or activate such as like
opening a door or interacting with an
object the reward signal provided by all
tasks is sparse the agent is only given
a positive extrinsic reward if it
extrinsic reward if it reaches a green
goal tile and otherwise making all
problems difficult from a reinforce
reinforcement learning perspective
because it's sparse and that's that's
like again at the very beginning like I
act I asked about the sparsity and what
is the the like I mean there's some
overarching like level of complexity
when there's a sparse set of rewards a
sparse set of problems a sparse set of
activated neurons I mean etc etc etc
right sparse networks are hard to deal
with mathematically and computationally
and I guess in terms of programming a
system with sparse learning it's
beneficial um it's seems that way anyway
okay so each problem has a specific time
step time step limit limit allotted to
allow the agent to complete the task so
you do it within a certain time or you
fail yeah very interesting there
sparsity in architecture space time
reward utility epistemic value all like
we don't live in Flat Lands we live on
the rough and variable
Peaks and the Very embodied constraints
and limitations of how things can
actually be connected to each other so
that's
wild cool okay so for the door key
problem agent must find the key um the
position of the key changes inside of a
locker room and then pick up the key in
order to unlock the door so it can leave
the room upon entering the second room
the agent must find the green tile in
order to successfully exit uh
terminating the episode by reaching the
goal state to receive a positive reward
um so they use a 6x6 grid the memory
task is a different test it's posed as a
memory test so in the memory test the
agent starts in a small room where it
can see an object a key or a ball um and
they in they modifi the problem to
ensure that the agent starts looking in
the direction of the object that's
interesting I wonder why like so that
they don't have to it does it just save
time like so you don't have to look
right look front look left look behind
you I I wonder why they modified the
problem in that way um so after
perceiving the object the agent has to
turn around Exit the room and go through
a narrow hallow that ends in a split at
the end of the split the agent can
either go up or down at the end of each
of these splits is a different object
either a key or a ball to successfully
complete the episode and receive a
positive reward the agent must remember
the initial object that it saw and go to
the split that contains the correct
matching object so did you see a key or
did you see a ball and then which way
are you going to go at the end of the
maze um and then they did a 7 by seven
grid for that one okay let's see what
they
found oh not
yet so these are the models that
comparison so they use their
model and a standard deep Q Network
model distillation and that's the
dqn R&D uh which is a curiosity model
and then a dqn that learns through
account count-based formulation of the
bbold exploration framework which we'll
have to learn more about in the dot too
so these are the models that they tested
against and then this is what they found
so success rate in the memory task for
the Cogan genen was like off the hook
like blew the other ones out of the
water right um like 98 success rate for
the memory task which is pretty crazy um
and then the door key task was I I guess
like zero for the dqn and then 100% 100%
100% for the other ones um or maybe then
the reverse so let's see from left to
right the door key task the memory task
in the bottom row is success rate over
the last 100 episodes the right is the
episode length oh there you go the
percentage in case of the maximum worst
case episode length so that is um dqn
having the worst right and then kogen
wasn't the fastest so oh yeah you can
see the episode that's I think it's just
a pure coincidence that this one's
100.0 but this is 100% Z like 100% and
this one's 100 time steps
0 but either way dqn does
worse than all three which can solve the
problems but of problem but the Cogan
gen is twice as good on the M problem
and then the episode lengths are pretty
comparable and ex the DQ yeah ex the D
is like takes forever right takes
forever and doesn't do very well in the
memory task um so yeah there you go all
right so that's how that's a lot of time
on the model and very little time on the
results uh and then this is just some
more of the results here so um you can
just see the the average reward episode
length um smooth for the door key
problem and the mem task which is the
right so the door key is the left the
memory task is the right um and here you
can see the Cog and gen on this bottom
one do you see this curve that is the um
the curve depicts a mean and standard
deviation over five
trials and the left is the average
reward I think oh yeah episodic reward
so that is the where we saw 98 for the
Cogen genen um and that's here too for
the door key
task remember memory task okay results
and discussion based on the results we
find that kog and Jen is able to learn
the grid World task the performance is
comparable to or on par with powerful
deep intrinsic curiosity reinforce
reinforcement learning methods that have
access to problem specific Global
Information and kog and genen can
successfully solve and outperform all
baselines on the memory task so Bravo we
have
arrived wow blue
what a
ride yeah what do you think about the
four paper the four paper uh
model well I can only return to what
Alex wrote in an
email which is it makes sense to have
done it how it was done I think it'd be
easy to look at a cognitive architecture
like this which integrates the
analytical components
and also these more psychological or
cognitive features like epistatic and
procedural memory it's easy to look at
that in a way that's disconnected from
the actual computational
implementation because connecting up the
formalism feels as easy as just writing
an equation or just drawing something
and then to say well maybe maybe the
working memory you know sends a message
to this other buffer it's like you can
just draw that out and nothing is going
to stop you but then the first three
papers kept it connected very closely to
the
actual locally
implementable
computation so then we were able to get
to this point of
um looking at such an interesting
cognitive model that's also
performance and be able to talk about
where it could be applied or what would
be different or limitations or like
these different features of this
but if it feels very different to look
at this after the first three which is
the research
Direction so I think it was a great
selection and I'm just looking forward
to talking with Alex what about
you yeah I'm looking forward to like
diving deeper into um the the models and
kind of understanding more about like
getting under the hood maybe so to speak
so what what makes them tick in a little
bit more detail so should be good cool
any other
comments awesome well thank you for
preparing and having fun working on
this. zero leading up to now and yeah in
the coming weeks we will proceed with
56.1 and point2 so thank you everybody
next
time